# **Aneta Martins**



aneta.martins@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/anetamartins



+44 7595 921203



https://github.com/AMartins87

### **Summary**

I am currently studying Full Stack Web Development Diploma at Code Institute. The syllabus includes HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and Python.

I have worked in events, office management roles for various companies, and as an executive assistant for a major food & beverage company for the past 14 years. I have been considering a career change for quite a while but there was never a good time. I have always had a knack for technology and web development seemed like the most challenging yet rewarding career choice.

#### **Experience**



# EA to Corporate Affairs Senior Director and Corporate Affairs & Communications Team Support

PepsiCo

Jun 2012 - Present (9 years 7 months +)

- PA support and extensive diary management to Corporate Affairs Senior Director, Communications Director and Head of External Affairs and ad-hoc support to the rest of UK communications team
- Supporting internal communications' projects and events
- Developing the weekly company newsletter and creating/uploading relevant internal story content
- Uploading content and maintaining PepsiCo UK website
- Recording internal & external measurements from the company's intranet site and social media
- Entering data in company's CRM system using Microsoft Dynamics 365
- Digital screens management
- ▶ Office 365 support including Teams, SharePoint & One Drive

## П

#### Office Manager

Ink N Toner UK

Nov 2009 - May 2012 (2 years 7 months)

- Assigning duties to office personnel
- Liaising with external suppliers
- Managing telephone/email queries and taking phone orders
- ► In charge of a customer review center
- Managing filing system and recurring revenue stream
- Maintaining supplies & equipment for the manufacturing department
- Work with Sage Line 50 accounting software
- ► Credit control

#### Manager Office

#### Optima Computer Centre Ltd

Oct 2007 - Oct 2009 (2 years 1 month)

- Front of house & first point of contact for visiting clients
- Handling telephone and email queries
- ► In charge of recurring revenue stream
- Scheduling engineer call outs and client follow-ups
- Running an internal CRM database

#### Event Coordinator

Charlton House / Zoological Society of London Jan 2007 - Sep 2007 (9 months)

- Organising visitor appointments
- Assisting during client meetings to discuss requirements & budget for an event
- · Selecting and negotiating with vendors to ascertain client's precise event requirements
- Assisting with the venue management; delegating event planning tasks to other staff members where necessary
- Overseeing event on the day, including problem-solving and guest inquiries before and during the event, directing event set-up
- Overseeing the dismantling, removal and clearing of the venue

#### **Education**



Full Stack Software Development
Jun 2021 - Jun 2022

## Business & Management College

A-Levels equivalent, Accounting and Business Management 2002 - 2006

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Awarding

IAO Level 2 Certificate in Understanding Nutrition and Health (QCF) - Innovate

Awarding

# 5 Day Coding Challenge - Code Institute

#### **Skills**

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Python (Programming Language) • Heroku • Bootstrap • WordPress